(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-23T22:06:21.122836",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
最高なメンバー
The best members,
上手くいかない日だって
even on days when things didn't go well,
解けていった
they gradually untangled.
教科書 水に落としたら
If I dropped my textbook in the water,
何だってやれそうだ
I felt like I could do anything.
落書きの中に光ってた思いを
The feelings that shone within the scribbles,
君と交わして描いた絵
the picture I drew after sharing them with you,
嘘みたいだな
it almost feels unreal.
描いて 記して
Drawing them, recording them...
夕暮れ
Dusk...
君のあたたかい手に 包まれたの
was wrapped in your warm hand.
手をつなぐ
Holding hands,
それだけで
just by doing that,
思いが伝わる
it feels as though
気がする
my feelings are conveyed.
段々と 増えていった
In the circle that gradually grew,
輪の中で 理由を考えて
I thought about the reason why.
大好きな
By the side
君の隣で
of you, whom I love so much,
楽しく過ごす日々を
the days spent joyfully...
ほら
Look,
一瞬で過ぎていく
they pass by in an instant,
昨日よりも加速してる
accelerating even more than yesterday.
ちゃんと繋いでて
Hold on tight.
簡単じゃないホームの
The cheer from a home
掛け声は
that isn't easy...
いつも君が明るく放って
You always brightly send it out,
支えていくね
supporting me.
ずっと
Forever,
刻まれて光るよ
it will be engraved and shine.
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1!
最高の始まり チャート
The chart of the best beginning
世界線を飛ばしたって
Even if we skip across timelines
理由を...
The reason...
遠くに届かせ
Reaching out into the distance
聞こえてきたんじゃない?
Can't you hear it now?
これがミュートする平成
This is the noise-muted era
ズレた世界揺らす
Shaking this shifted world
もう一回
One more time
まだ冷めないで
Don't cool down yet
この指に止まれ
Gather around me
追いついて
Catch up to me
SHOWTIME!
まだ物足りない
It's still not enough
エピソードのない
Without an episode
もう一回
One more time
もう待てない
Can't wait any longer
今すぐ
Right now
焦って 繊細
Anxious yet delicate
限界突破
Breaking past limits
最高の始まり チャート
The chart of the best beginning
世界線を飛ばしたって
Even if we skip across timelines
日々の音色が
The daily melodies
響いていくんだ
Keep resounding loud
一緒に未来へジャンプして
Jump into the future together
枠を飛び出して
Breaking out of the box
生きよう 誰の心だって
Let's live on, connecting every heart
共鳴感情
Resonating feelings
この声を重ねてよ
Layer your voice with mine
夢の信号
Signals of dreams
響く音は
The echoing sound is...
鳴らしたんだ この感情
Resonating this emotion
アナログに変換して
Converting it to analog
キラキラ愛らしく
Sparkling so adorably
最高は一秒 止められない
The best moments can't be stopped for a second
この状態
In this state of mind
探したい
I want to search for it
手作りの世界が
A handmade world
望むバタフライ
Desiring butterflies
変えに行きたいよ
I want to go change it
電波を押し込められない
Waves that can't be contained
この状態
In this state of mind
教えて
Tell me
焦って 繊細
Anxious yet delicate
限界突破
Breaking past limits
最先端 突き抜けて
Piercing through the cutting edge
世界線 モニター越しの
Across timelines, through the monitor
日々の熱感を感じて
Feeling the warmth of every day
ここから招待
Inviting you from here
最高を更新させて
Let us update the absolute best
位置調整
Adjusting positions
今夜のパーティーを試してよ
Try out tonight's party
再起形態になって
Transforming into restart mode
新証明を試して
Trying out a new proof
君に愛を届けて
Sending love to you
接続を壊す
Breaking the connection
繋がっていって
Connecting together
未知の存在を認めてよ
Acknowledge this unknown existence
共鳴感情
Resonating feelings
この声を重ねてよ
Layer your voice with mine
夢の信号
Signals of dreams
響く音は
The echoing sound is...
回っているよ 回っているよ
Spinning around, spinning around...
描いたキャンバスに
On the painted canvas
あなたはまだひとりぼっち
You are still all alone
一歩を踏み出していこう
Let's take a step forward
ここから始まったストーリー
The story that started from here
夢で見た景色は
The scenery seen in a dream
憧れを叶えて
Fulfilling that longing
回っているよ 回っているよ
Spinning around, spinning around
この広域の空で
In this vast open sky
あの日から君が見た声を
The voice you saw since that day
辿り着く頃
By the time we arrive
祈ってるよ 祈ってるよ
I'm praying, I'm praying
夢の目覚めていく
Awakening from the dream
一言が
A single word
届いて...
Reaches out...
世界は広がって
The world expands wide
まだたくさんの明日がある
There are still so many tomorrows
夢みたいな色で
In dreamlike colors
まだまだ追いかけ続けて
Keep on chasing endlessly
チャレンジは止まらない
The challenge never stops
点と点で線を繋げて
Connecting lines from point to point
踊っているよ 踊っているよ
I'm dancing, I'm dancing
今もずっとここで
Still right here all this time
いつかの日が
So that one day
君が見つけてくれるように
You will find me
踊っているよ 踊っているよ
I'm dancing, I'm dancing
時空を超えて
Transcending time and space
君の元へ
To where you are,
届いて
may it reach you...
待ってるよ 待ってるよ 待ってるよ 時が変わっても
I'm waiting, waiting, waiting, even if time changes.
同じ星が奏でた音と ぴったりな言葉
The perfect words to match the sound played by the same star.
寂しくても 何度でも 歓声を原動力に変えて
Even if it's lonely, turning cheers into power time and again,
ここまで歩んできた 私なら
if it's us who walked all the way here...
私 待ってるよ 待ってるよ 待ってるよ
I'm waiting, waiting, waiting,
この広い空で
in this vast sky.
あの日から君のこと想った通り
Just as I've thought of you since that day,
待ってるよ 待ってるよ 待ってるよ
I'm waiting, waiting, waiting,
目指したままの場所で
at the place we always aimed for.
君の元へ 届いて
Reach to where you are,
夢をどうか 叶えて
please make our dream come true.
みんな！この曲待ってたでしょ？
Everyone! You were waiting for this song, right?
しっかり掛け声覚えてきたよね！
You practiced all the chants, right?
一緒に「ふっふー」って盛り上がっちゃおう！
Let me hear you shout "Fu-fuu" together!
せーの！
Ready, set, go!
われらの空の始まりは
The beginning of our sky was
惚れた瞬間 あらららら
the moment we fell in love, oh my!
あーこれは困った 二度と元に戻らない 大問題
Ah, this is trouble—a huge problem that can't be undone.
そして星が生まれまして
And then a star was born,
宇宙の角の一本松は
a lone pine tree at the corner of the universe.
あなたと出会った これ次元を歪むくらいな変
Meeting you—this is so weird it distorts dimensions.
このまま母船を打ち上げて どこまでも高い空へ飛び出そう
Let's launch the mothership as it is and leap into the sky high above!
さあ さあ さあ 咲いたこの愛は あなたがくれた熱を持ったステーション
Now, now, now, this bloomed love is a station filled with your warmth.
あなたに言ってしまって
Saying it out loud to you,
出会ったさっさっさっさを数える ほら目の前にずっとある 一生性
counting all our quick encounters, look, a lifetime lies right before us.
出ろ！ 満ちろ！ このビッグバンに気づいて！
Burst out! Overflow! Realize this big bang!
愛は地球ぐらいに膨らんでこんなになってんぞ！
Love has expanded as big as the Earth, growing like this!
そこらへんの奴は この愛のために生きて
Everyone around here lives for this love!
ずっと推し あなたのハッピー祈り 今のままでいいよみたいな顔して
Always supporting you, praying for your happiness, looking like "it's fine as it is."
めっちゃめっちゃ大好き！ ちょっとの反応の差を喜ぶ姿
I love you so, so much! Watching you rejoice over the slightest reaction...
嘘？こんなの逃すなんてなんておぞましい
No way? Missing out on this would be terrifying!
われらの星の活動は
Our star's activities
割とつづいて
continue on quite well.
いや それはすごいな つまりあなたと私の創世記
Wow, that's amazing—in short, it's the genesis of you and me.
このまま母船をあなたごと連れて行かれて お目覚めした
Carried away along with the mothership together with you, awakening.
さあ さあ さあ としたこの愛は あなたがねえ今頃超心配してた
Now, now, now, this love was something you were super worried about by now.
知ってた？ これ今日まで続くんだ
Did you know? This continues to this very day.
出会ったさっさっさっさを数えて いささか眩しく輝く一生性
Counting all our quick encounters, a lifetime shining brilliantly.
あなたと！ 私で！ ビッグバン事態の！
With you! And me! In a Big Bang situation!
愛は地球ぐらいに膨らんでこんなになってんぞ！
Love has expanded as big as the Earth, growing like this!
そこらへんの奴は この愛のために生き
Everyone around here wants to live
たい！
for this love!
みんなー！
Everyone!
見えてるー？ 聞こえてるー？
Can you see me? Can you hear me?
はい、というわけで
Alright, so then,
今日も2日目！そらぱ2025ですよー！
Today is day two! It's SoraPa 2025!
みんな今歌いきっちゃった... 見えてる？聞こえてる？
Everyone, I just finished singing... Can you see me? Can you hear me?
可愛い、ありがとう！
So cute, thank you!
返事上手ー！
You're so good at responding!
昨日もやりましたが、今日もね、掛け声みんなでやっていきましょうね！
We did this yesterday too, but today as well, let's all do the calls together!
いやー、というわけで、1年半ぶりなんですよ。
Wow, so yeah, it's been a year and a half.
ま、昨日ぶりだから、まあ1日ぶりですね！
Well, since yesterday, so actually just one day!
今日も2日目だよーって人！
Who here is attending day two as well?
今日が初めてだよーって人！
Who here is attending for the first time today?
そもそもライブ自体初めてですよーって人！
Who here is attending a live concert for the very first time?
じゃあ、ライブデビューですね！ありがとうございます！
So it's your live concert debut! Thank you so much!
では全員に声出してもらいたいな！とりあえず、全員！
Now I want everyone to make some noise! First off, everyone!
声出せるかな？出せなかったら手振るだけでいいよね！
Can you shout out? If you can't, just waving your hands is fine, right?
女の子ー！
Girls!
おー！ありがとう！
Oh, thank you!
男の子ー！
Boys!
未成年席ー！
Minors' section!
海外の皆さんー！
Everyone overseas!
コメントー！
People in the comments!
今「イエイイエイ」って言ってくれてる！そして、左の皆さん！
You're saying "Yay yay" right now! And everyone on the left!
右の皆さん！
Everyone on the right!
全員ー！
Everyone!
いやー、最高じゃないですか！みんな、声枯らす準備できてるって感じ？
Wow, isn't this amazing? Are you all ready to lose your voices?
見えてる見えてる、前のほう、後ろのほう、前のほう、後ろのほう...
I can see you, I can see you! Front side, back side, front side, back side...
どこ見てんだろうね！
Where am I looking, right?
あ、ありがとう！ありがとう！ありがとう！
Ah, thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
いや、みんなのね、応援も、今日なんかザリティ率高いね。めちゃくちゃ青い。
Everyone's support too—today there's a high ratio of Zariti penlights! It's super blue.
なんか世界が青い。あ、ザリティじゃないのかな？もしかしてあれかな？
Like the world is blue. Ah, maybe they aren't Zariti? Could it be...
今回のライブのTシャツの人もいる？
Are there people wearing this concert's T-shirt too?
あ、やっぱそうだよね！Tシャツも青だもんね！すごい、ありがとうございます！
Ah, I thought so! The T-shirt is blue too, right? Awesome, thank you so much!
ねー！みんなが外で写真撮って「今から待ちきれない」って
Right! I saw you all taking photos outside saying "I can't wait"...
やってるの、すごい見てましたから！ありがとうございます！
I was watching you do that! Thank you so much!
とね、こうやって喋ってるんですが...
And so, while I'm talking like this...
YouTubeをご覧の皆様...
To everyone watching on YouTube...
なんと... まだ来たばかりなんだけどね。
Believe it or not... we've only just started though.
本当に3曲しかやってないから、まだ来たばかりかもしれないね。
We've really only done three songs, so it might feel like we've only just begun.
物足りないなーと思う人、ぜひね、どこ... ここ？
For those who feel it's not enough, please... where, here?
どっかに概要欄があるので、そこから配信チケット買って続きを見てもらえると、
There's a description section somewhere, so if you buy a stream ticket from there and watch the rest,
私... あ、噛んだ(笑)。とっても嬉しいなと思います！
I would... Ah, I stumbled on my words (laughs). I'd be super happy!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
というわけで、早速ね、おしゃべりばっかりしてたらただの雑談枠になっちゃうのでね！
So then, if I just keep chatting, this will just turn into a casual talk stream!
次の曲目に行こうと思うんですが...
So I'd like to move on to the next song...
まあね、昨日歌ってなくて待ってた曲あるんじゃない？
Well, isn't there a song I didn't sing yesterday that you've been waiting for?
次の曲は、新アルバムからダンサブルな、ダンスダンスダンスな曲を歌ってみようと思います！
For the next song, I'm going to sing a danceable, dance-dance-dance song from my new album!
ご視聴頂きまして、ありがとうございました。本日の公演は終了いたしました。
[Thank you for watching. Today's performance has ended.]
あー...
Ah...
感情めちゃくちゃの 蜃気楼に手を伸ばさ...
Reaching out my hand to a wild mirage...
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。★ライブチケット購入はコチラ>> SPWN
[The free initial stream ends here. ★Purchase live tickets here >> SPWN]
冒頭無料配信はこちらで終了です。
The free preview stream ends here.